[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
[Arnaldo] It's just us now!
You're mine! You're all mine!
[Diego] Get your hands off my wife!
[Lily] As long as you live,
no one will ever love you, Arnaldo!
No one! Because you're a monster!
Even if you let me live,
I will never love you!
I will never love a criminal!
-[screams]
-[gunshot]
[Julio] Blood will be paid with blood.
I promise you that, Arnaldo.
No!
[Diego] Because of what he did,
it's like he paid for all the crimes
he committed.
He will never hurt anyone again.
[gunshots]
[Julio] I'm coming for you!
I will be coming for each
and every one of you!
[Lily] Arnaldo's death
just goes to show that
whether you're rich or poor,
powerful or weak,
what you do to others
will always come back to you.
[Julio] Rest now, my prince,
for I will burn the whole town
of Ardiente to ashes
to avenge your death.
-[Diego] Get away from there!
-[explosion]
Snap out of your insanity!
Help me and your son, Arnaldo!
Make them pay! They killed me!
Wake up, Ma! Wake up!
[Edna] This way, sir.
What's taking Ronald so long?
Where is he?
I have no idea.
But I really hope he finds the Torillos.
Don't worry.
He knows we're supposed to meet.
Let's just wait.
[Efren] Let's just start
planning our next move.
-[Ronald] Everyone.
-He's here.
Ronald.
It's confirmed.
I've found Lily and Diego Torillo's house.
This is our chance.
But we still don't know
what they're planning.
[ominous music]
Pleased to meet you.
I've been wanting to meet
Red Dragon's daughter for so long.
The pleasure is mine.
My mother gave me the password
to the Triad database.
She gave this to me before she died.
[suspenseful music]
She also left me in charge
of the syndicate.
I'll need all your support,
so Papa and I can revive it.
What do you need from us?
I need your three G's.
Guns, goons, and gold.
I want lots of it.
This is their house. Leave it to me.
Sir, my companions are hoping
to talk to Diego and Miss Lily.
I'm sorry, but we don't know
who your companions are.
But they have something
important to tell them.
Can you just tell them we're outside?
[Fernan] It's important.
We wouldn't have come here if--
Diego! Miss Lily!
Good evening.
These people are looking for you.
They say they have
something important to tell you.
-Okay, let them in.
-Thank you, sir.
Please come in.
Come. I told you so.
You wouldn't even let us in.
[Fernan] Here they are.
What brings you here?
We're the relatives
of the Ardientes' victims.
We don't believe the accusations
Julio made against you.
We want to help you fight them.
[pensive music playing]
[Ronald] Our parents were
newspaper columnists.
We were still kids when
the Ardientes had them abducted.
-Let go of me!
-Mom!
-Mom! Mom!
-Edna!
Mom!
Edna! No!
-Mom!
-Kids…
-Get up! Move!
-…we'll come back.
Edna!
-Dad!
-Ronald!
-Kids!
-Mom!
-Hurry up!
-My children! We'll come back!
-Ronald!
-We'll come back!
Mom!
Dad!
-Don't take them!
-Mom!
Mom!
We never saw them again.
We believe they were murdered after that.
But we weren't able to file a case
because we couldn't find their bodies.
They took care of any evidence
that could implicate the Ardientes.
[woman] Shush now.
[Edna] We left the country fearing
the Ardientes would come for us next.
So, kids, are you ready?
Yes.
Help me put their luggage in the car.
[Edna] We tried starting anew,
and left our past behind.
Let's go.
But, then, we saw you on TV.
[Ronald] We saw how you
fought the Ardientes.
Then, all the bad memories
came flooding back.
Those Ardientes are despicable.
They're rotten to the core.
We have to go back.
[Edna] We could no longer turn our backs
on what was happening back home.
That's why we came back.
We met up with the relatives
of their other victims.
Edna, this is Efren.
His family was one of Ardientes' victims.
Please take a seat.
-I'm Edna.
-My name's Efren.
The others should be here soon.
Oh, here they are.
This is Mister Ben and Mrs. Gloria.
-Ben.
-Hi, I'm Ronald.
I'm Efren.
-I'm Ronald.
-Hey, nice to meet you.
We want to fight back.
All of us here have relatives,
friends, and loved ones
who are still missing
ever since the Ardientes
took them away from us.
Hold on.
They've done even worse things
to the rest of us.
At least Ronald and Edna here
still have each other.
What about me?
The Ardientes had my wife, my child,
and even my parents killed.
They took everyone in my life away.
They ruined my life.
[Gloria] Just like you, Miss Lily,
we're all looking for justice
for our loved ones.
We need to find out what happened to them.
Since we're all victims here,
we will help each other out.
My family and I promise…
to help you all look for
your missing loved ones.
We've heard rumors.
Apparently, the Ardientes have
a mass grave hidden somewhere.
A place where they bury
most of their victims.
Miss Lily, our parents
might be buried there.
[tense music playing]
[ominous music]
Hi, Papa.
Your favorite daughter is back.
And, by the way, I've already
gained the Triad's support.
[suspenseful music playing]
Welcome home.
You know, I knew somehow
you'd be able to get back on your feet.
Oh, Papa, spare me this nonsense.
Do you think I've forgotten
the things you've done?
I swear on my mother, husband, and my son,
I will fight this with you.
But this time around,
you will treat me as your equal.
Whatever you want, my dear daughter.
All I want is my revenge.
Good. Since we're on the same page.
Now, I want the ugly heads
of Diego and Lily Torillo.
Do you still think they can help us?
Where is this fight headed, anyway?
Ben, no one can help us except Lily Cruz!
She's right, Ben. Let's trust Lily Cruz.
Lily Cruz?
What if the Ardientes find out about this?
Can Lily Cruz protect us?
If not, we'll be tossed into
that mass grave too.
We're taking this risk for our loved ones.
But this is a fight we can't win!
We'll just end up dead
like the rest of them!
-Ben!
-Ben.
We're in this together,
and we will find a way.
-[woman] He's right.
-Have some faith.
We're risking our lives
so we can finally get justice.
-That's true.
-Yes, Ben. Calm down.
We need to be united, not divided.
Sure.
Keep fooling yourselves,
and believe you'll get justice!
But I'm not getting my hopes up
for nothing again!
I don't want to experience
the Ardientes' cruelty again!
What?
-Ben.
So much for solidarity.
Maybe we can still change his mind.
We just need to talk to him.
[tense music playing]
[Lily] Based on the records,
Ronald and Edna's parents
were last seen in this area.
This is where the other victims
were last seen.
Most of the rumors point
to this area as the mass grave.
That's around one kilometer
away from here.
Even if it takes us months,
years, or decades,
we will find that mass grave.
We will find the victims
and help the loved ones they left behind.
The Ardientes will pay for their crimes.
That's why we need to find
the mass grave soon.
-Papa.
-[loads gun]
I gave you the men, the guns,
and everything else you need.
Why are Diego and Lily still alive?
Are you up to it?
Or is old age making you soft,
and you're ready for retirement?
Just tell me, and I'll get
the job done myself.
[chuckles]
The battle has already been won, Emilia.
Their names are already written
in the obituary.
I'm just waiting…
for the right time to strike.
The time is now, Papa.
I'll finish this once and for all.
Emilia…
you do not give orders
to the captain of the ship.
Oh, correction, Papa.
I am the co-captain of the ship, remember?
We had an agreement.
If it wasn't for me, Papa,
this ship would have sunk a long time ago.
[Emilia sighs]
It's useless talking to you.
We're going to the families
of the victims.
We're going to protect them.
Then Mom and I will head to the site.
We might find the mass grave there.
[Camia] We can't wait any longer.
We need to act before Julio
finds out what we're up to.
-Be careful.
-You too.
If only I could stay by your side,
so I could protect you, I would.
But, you're right.
This fight is bigger than both of us.
We're helping so many people.
This will be the biggest case
Julio Ardiente will face
if we find that mass grave.
He will pay for his crimes.
We'll take him down.
Just remember our promise
to each other, Diego.
No one leaves…
…and no one gets left behind.
Governor.
He's here.
Let him in.
[ominous music building]
Have a seat.
What did you want to tell me
about Lily and Diego?
Show me the money first.
Magbanua.
Twenty million pesos.
As agreed upon, for your service.
Now…
tell me what you know.
Lily and Diego know about the mass grave.
They're planning to expose
the hundreds of people
your family has killed.
[laughs]
Truth is, Ben…
The only time they'll see that mass grave…
is when I drop their corpses
down that pit.
Only then will they find the mass grave.
But, before that happens…
I will make them pay
for what they did to Arnaldo.
Magbanua.
Prepare our men.
I want the people of Ardiente to witness…
just how I'll mete out my punishment
and wrath on Lily and Diego.
[ominous music]
Villanueva, you're in charge of
protecting Lily and her mother.
Make sure nothing happens to them.
Yes, sir.
We'll get going.
Anna, Marlon.
Please be careful.
Anna, Marlon, let's go.
Okay.
Anna.
What's wrong?
I don't know if I should
text Jepoy or not.
He might be able to help us.
If he wanted to help,
he would be here by now.
And stop relying on people who don't care.
You should rely on the
people who are here.
[soft music playing]
Let's go?
[sensual music]
I love you, Madrigal.
I love you so much.
I love you too, Anna.
What?!
What did you just say?
Did you just say "Anna"?
Huh?!
Did you say "Anna"?
[stammers] I'm sorry.
Sorry, Natalie.
-[shouts]
-Ouch.
-Ouch. Sorry! Sorry!
-[Natalie groaning]
[Natalie cries]
Natalie!
Hey, Natalie.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-[continues crying]
Natalie.
That's my name.
Do you want me
to spell out my name for you?
It's…
Do you want me to carve…
each letter on your skin…
so that you won't forget my name?
I'm sorry.
Get out!
[Natalie grunts, cries]
[soft music playing]
[grunting]
I really love you, Anna.
I need to see you.
[soft music continues]
[tense music playing]
The mass grave could be around here.
We'll check this area.
[ominous music playing]
Lily?
Anna?
Anna!
Where is everyone?
-Lily?
-[door opens]
Where are Anna and Lily?
They went to see the relatives
of the Ardientes' victims.
Tell me where they are.
[Gloria] Ronald.
Is it true they finally found
the mass grave?
Lily Cruz thinks she knows where it is.
They're going there right now.
I called you all here today
to ask for help.
What are we waiting for?
Let's go.
So we can finally expose
what those Ardientes did
to our loved ones.
-That's right.
-Right.
Hold on.
What if they come back for us?
How long are we just going to hide?
It's time for us to fight the Ardientes.
That's right.
Friends, Ronald and Edna are right.
It's time for us
to stand up to the Ardientes.
[Ronald] That's right.
-Everything will be fine.
-Have faith.
[indistinct]
[tense music playing]
You guys stay here.
Stand guard.
-Yes, sir.
Let's go.
[tense music playing]
-[door kicked open]
-[people exclaim]
What's this?! What's going on here?!
[screams]
What's the meaning of this?
[goon] Don't resist, and do what we say.
Who called this meeting?!
Answer me!
Are you plotting something
against the Ardientes?
Idiots.
What are you waiting for?
Take them.
-Get up!
-Hurry!
-Hurry up!
-Quick!
-Get up!
-Hurry! Get up!
You! Get up!
Go out right now!
Wait. Hold on.
[tense music continues]
Those are the Ardientes' men.
Batch, come with me.
-Okay.
-Anna, you stay here.
No matter what happens, just stay here.
Keep Anna safe.
Be careful.
We will.
[Diego] Batch.
Batch, they aren't looking.
Where are those two?
They were just here.
Come on. Let's look for them!
-Let's go.
-Take that side.
[tense music intensifies]
Batch, take this.
Get them all down there!
Go! Go!
Move it!
-[goon 1] Go down!
-[goon 2] Take them! Hurry!
[goon 2] Go down!
[goon 1] Come on!
-Move faster!
-So slow! Hurry!
-On your knees! Hurry!
-Faster! Faster!
-Get down!
-Hurry!
Get down!
I said get down!
Thought you could get away?
-Where are the guards?!
-On the ground!
Where are the men I stationed here?!
[goon 3] Boss, we can't find them!
[tense music intensifies]
-Batch.
-Come on. Let's go.
-One. Two.
-Two.
[both] Three.
[grunts]
[gunfire]
-[clamoring]
-[gunfire continues]
-Ma'am, wait here!
-No! We need to help them!
[gunfire continues]
Anna?
-[gunfire continues]
-[people clamoring]
[gunfire continues]
[women exclaiming]
Don't move.
[action music playing]
-They're getting away!
-Let's get them!
[women speaking indistinctly]
Where do you think you're going?
Hey! Come back here!
Let go of me!
[Anna groans]
Let's finish her off!
[suspenseful music]
Anna!
Anna! Anna! Anna.
Rosanna. Anna!
Anna! Anna!
Anna!
Anna! Anna! Anna!
Rosanna Navarro. It's me, Jepoy.
If you can hear me, I still love you.
Anna. Rosanna!
Rosanna.
Rosanna, hey.
Anna?
[somber music playing]
[Jepoy] Hey, Anna.
Jepoy, I'll take it from here.
Jepoy, come on.
Anna.
Anna, please wake up.
[Marlon] Anna, wake up.
Anna.
Anna, it's me, Marlon.
Go ahead.
Anna.
[Marlon whispers] Anna.
[somber music continues]
Are you okay?
Anna, are you okay?
[tense music playing]
[tires screech]
[gunshot]
[Camia gasps]
-Duck!
-[Camia yelps]
[gunfire continues]
Mom, our guns.
[tense music continues]
Mom, hurry.
[Lily] Take my mother away from here.
Get away from here! Go to Diego.
Tell him Julio's men ambushed us.
Lily, I can't just leave you here.
Mom, please, you're our only hope.
I'll be right behind you.
All right. I promise
I'll come back for you.
-I love you so much.
-[gunshots]
Hurry! Get my mother out of here!
[dramatic music]
[music intensifies]
-[Camia yelps]
-[gunshots]
Arnaldo, I want to clear a path
for your comeback.
So that you can fulfill
all of your lifelong dreams.
And let's face it.
Let's face the truth.
Age is creeping up on me.
And I'm ready to turn over
the baton of leadership to you.
I'll be the one carrying on
the family's legacy.
I promise you that.
And that has always been my dream.
Thank you so much.
-Viva Ardiente.
-[glasses clink]
-[Julio chuckles]
I remember…
I used to have a drinking partner.
Wherever you are, Arnaldo,
cheers.
[sighs]
[phone rings]
Yes?
Governor, we have Lily Cruz.
[chuckles]
Yeah. Okay.
[exhales, sniffles]
[exhales]
Lily Cruz…
you're starting to bore me.
It turns out, you're not as intelligent
as I thought you were.
You're either dumb…
or you've got a handful of bodyguards…
who are stupid.
Just like that…
my man, Magbanua, was able to get you?
This is unforgivable.
I expected more from you,
Lily Cruz.
Death isn't enough
to punish the people
who killed my grandson.
What will be more satisfying
than their death
is the suffering I will make them feel.
Big mistake, Lily Cruz.
When you took the life…
of Arnaldo.
You think you know pain,
Lily Cruz?
You've never felt the kind of pain
that I'm going to make you feel.
Now you will feel the
wrath of Julio Ardiente.
[suspenseful music]
[Diego's phone rings]
-[line ringing]
-[Camia panting]
-Diego.
-[line ringing]
[ominous music]
Thank you for saving us, Diego.
We're really grateful
that we're all safe and sound.
We'll always be here to help you.
[somber piano music]
-Thank you very much.
-You're welcome.
Anna! Anna! Rosanna Navarro.
[soft music playing]
Anna.
Is there a problem?
I heard you say my name earlier.
I don't remember mentioning anything.
So, you weren't the one who saved me.
I saw you lying there
unconscious so I helped you.
But you're right, Anna.
I'm not the one who saved you.
Rosanna.
Only two people know my real name.
It's Lily and Jepoy.
[crowd chanting] Justice for the mayor!
Justice for the mayor!
[crowd continues chanting]
We're here to--
Citizens of Poblacion Ardiente,
do any of you believe…
the claims of our vile enemies?
That your beloved Mayor Arnaldo
killed himself?!
[crowd chant] No! We don't believe them!
We don't believe them!
-They're all liars!
-It's not true!
-Liars!
-We don't believe them!
[man] Señor Julio,
we're here to support you!
This is too much.
My grandson's already dead.
And they still want to ruin his image.
Your mayor is gone.
Yet, here they are, destroying his memory.
They've gone too far.
This is the last time they will hurt us.
I only have one request.
Let's all meet at the capitol.
Call all your relatives.
-[man] Let's go to the capitol.
-[Julio] Call your children.
Call all your friends.
Because today,
we will get justice!
Today, we will punish…
the real criminal!
The murderer who killed Mayor Arnaldo!
On this day…
we will punish…
Lily Cruz!
-Punish her!
-Justice for Mayor Arnaldo!
[indistinct shouting]
[crowd speaking indistinctly]
[unintelligible]
[crowd] Viva Ardiente!
We're making sure the Ardientes' men
won't be able to escape.
You'll testify against the Ardientes,
and admit they sent you here.
You won't get anything from me.
You know what?
You're just wasting your time.
No one can ever defeat the Ardientes.
Justice and truth will always prevail!
You're only strengthening
our determination
to fight the Ardientes!
The truth will come out eventually.
Everyone will discover how vile
the Ardientes truly are.
Keep dreaming, because
the Ardientes are here to stay.
[tense music playing]
[Camia groans]
[yelping]
[yelps, groans]
[tense music]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music playing]
-You killed him!
-Is it hard to accept, Julio?!
Your beloved grandson killed himself
because he couldn't stomach
being the monster…
-…you turned him into!
-[Julio shouts]
[man] Listen up, everyone!
The governor wants us
to head over to the plaza.
He said they will bring Lily Cruz there
and punish her
for murdering our mayor!
Let us show our support for the Ardientes!
-We will be one…
-[crowd] Viva Ardiente!
[Julio] Everyone, behold
the cancer afflicting this town.
Lily Cruz!
-[indistinct shouting]
-[woman] You killed our mayor!
You're a murderer!
You deserve to be punished!
[theme music fades]